homemade-circuits.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for Homemade Circuit Projects**  
At https://homemade-circuits.com/ we consider the privacy of our visitors to be **extremely important**. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information collected and recorded by https://homemade-circuits.com/ and how we use it.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, https://homemade-circuits.com/ makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services's analytics.

The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks.

This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information.

IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

 **How Google uses information from www.homemade-circuits.com**

 **www.homemade-circuits.com** uses Google services to improve their content and keep it free. By integrating Google services,  **www.homemade-circuits.com** shares information with Google.

For example, when you visit a website such as  **www.homemade-circuits.com** that uses advertising services like AdSense, including analytics tools like Google Analytics, or embeds video content from YouTube, your web browser automatically sends certain information to Google. This includes the URL of the page you’re visiting and your IP address. We may also [set cookies on your browser](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/cookies/) or read cookies that are already there.

Apps that use Google advertising services also share information with Google, such as the name of the app and a unique identifier for advertising.

Google uses the information shared by sites and apps to deliver our services, maintain and improve them, develop new services, measure the effectiveness of advertising, protect against fraud and abuse, and personalize content and ads you see on Google and on our partners’ sites and apps. See our [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) to learn more about how we process data for each of these purposes and our [Advertising](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) page for more about Google ads, how your information is used in the context of advertising, and how long Google stores this information.

 **Ad personalization**

If ad personalization is turned on, Google will use your information to make your ads more useful for you. For example, a website that sells mountain bikes might use Google's ad services. After you visit that site, you could see an ad for mountain bikes on a different site that shows ads served by Google.

If ad personalization is off, Google will not collect or use your information to create an ad profile or personalize the ads Google shows to you. You will still see ads, but they may not be as useful.

Ads may still be based on the topic of the website or app you're looking at, your current search terms, or on your general location, but not on your interests, search history, or browsing history. Your information can still be used for the other purposes mentioned above, such as to measure the effectiveness of advertising and protect against fraud and abuse.

When you interact with a website or app that uses Google services, you may be asked to choose whether you want to see personalized ads from ad providers, including Google.

Regardless of your choice, Google will not personalize the ads you see if your ad personalization setting is off or your account is ineligible for personalized ads.

You can see and control what information we use to show you ads by visiting your [ad settings](https://adssettings.google.com/).

 **How you can control the information collected by Google on these sites and apps**

Here are some of the ways you can control the information that is shared by your device when you visit or interact with sites and apps that use Google services:

  * [Ad Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/) helps you control ads you see on Google services (such as Google Search or YouTube), or on non-Google websites and apps that use Google ad services. You can also [learn how](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) ads are personalized, opt out of ad personalization, and block specific advertisers.
  * If you are signed in to your Google Account, and depending on your Account settings, [My Activity](https://myactivity.google.com/myactivity) allows you to review and control data that’s created when you use Google services, including the information we collect from the sites and apps you have visited. You can browse by date and by topic, and delete part or all of your activity.
  * Many websites and apps use Google Analytics to understand how visitors engage with their sites or apps. If you don’t want Analytics to be used in your browser, you can [install the Google Analytics browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Learn more about [Google Analytics and privacy](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245).
  * [Incognito mode in Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95464) allows you to browse the web without recording webpages and files in your browser or Account history (unless you choose to sign in). Cookies are deleted after you've closed all of your incognito windows and tabs, and your bookmarks and settings are stored until you delete them. Learn more about [cookies.](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/cookies/)
  * Many browsers, including Chrome, allow you to block third-party cookies. You can also clear any existing cookies from within your browser. Learn more about [managing cookies in Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647).

 **Comment Cookies**

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices.

Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there.  
This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

### Caching

This site utilizes caching in order to facilitate a faster response time and better user experience. Caching potentially stores a duplicate copy of every web page that is on display on this site.

All cache files are temporary, and are never accessed by any third party, except as necessary to obtain technical support from the cache plugin vendor. Cache files expire on a schedule set by the site administrator, but may easily be purged by the admin before their natural expiration, if necessary.

 **Please Note:**

The author or the admin of this website personally **does not collect any information** from the visitors. Whatever information are collected it could be by the 3rd party plugins and softwares as explained above, which are mandatory for enabling proper functioning of this website.

 **Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.
